Guide to the Legacy Community Health /Montrose Center records MS 701
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Legacy Community Health/Montrose Center records
1980-2000
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Legacy Community Health
MS 701
2.5 Linear Feet 3 boxes
The Montrose Center records comprise meeting minutes, Board business, and community services-related records within the date range of 1980 to 2000. Total size is 2.5 linear feet, 3 boxes.
Biographical / Historical
Legacy Community Health Services opened its new state-of-the-art 40,000 square foot clinic, the Montrose Center, in September 2011. It brings together two current clinic locations, allowing access to primary and behavioral healthcare services, eye care, wellness services, a gym and new dental care. The medical facility houses eight speciality clinics, ten support programs, four education based community programs and a pharmacy, and began servicing patients on Sept. 12, followed by its grand opening on Oct. 16. It offers pediatrics, pediatric behavioral health, family planning, HIV/STD testing and counseling, HIV specialty care, and a variety of support programs for people living with AIDS. Legacy operates three related facilities, Southwest Clinic, Baker-Ripley Clinic, and Lyons Avenue Health Center.
Scope and Contents
The Montrose Center records comprise meeting minutes, Board business, and community services-related records within the date range of 1980 to 2000. Total size is 2.5 linear feet, 3 boxes.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored onsite at the Woodson Research Center.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This material was donated by Legacy Community Health Services, Katy Caldwell CFO, on Sept. 26, 2017.
Arrangement
Materials in this collection have been arranged in three series: Series I: Meeting minutes and supporting materials; Series II: Board business; Series III: Community services
Index Terms
Subjects
Health care and medicine; LGBTQ people
Document Types
minutes (administrative records)
Places
AIDS (Disease) - Patients; AIDS
- Series I: Board minutes and supporting materials
  - 1982 January-May (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1982 June-August (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1982 September-December (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1983 January-April (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1983 May-July (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1983 August-December (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1984 January-May (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1984 June-December (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1985 January-May (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1985 July-December (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1986 January-May (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1986 June-December (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1987 January-June (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1987 July-December (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1988 January-May (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 1988 June-December (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 1989 January-April (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1989 May-August (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1989 September-December (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1990 January-April (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1990 May-September (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1990 October-December (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1991 January-April (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1991 May-September (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1991 October-December (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1994 April-June (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1994 July, November, December (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 1995 January-April (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 1995 July-September (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 1995 October-December (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 2005 July-December (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 2006 January-June (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Series II: Board business
  - Board meeting attendance (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Board orientation book (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Board member terms (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - "Evaluating the Combination of the Assistance Fund and Montrose Clinic" (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - "HIV+ Community Needs Assessment", 1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Reorganization proposal, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Cumulative demographics, 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Finance Committee (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Series III: Community Services
  - Sub-series A: Activity reports
    - 1994 October, December (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - 1995 January, February, April, May (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 1995 July, September, October, November (Box 3, Folder 11)